<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<SourceAnalyzer Name="+ Extended Original Rules">
	<Description>
		Rules that are based on the original ones with adding some exception cases.
	</Description>
	<Rules>
		<Rule Name="ElementMustBeginWithUpperCaseLetter" CheckId="EX1300" DisabledByDefault="true">
			<Context>{0} names begin with an upper-case letter: {1}.</Context>
			<Description>Validates that names of certain types of elements begin with an upper-case letter. Based on SA1300 behaviour, but allows windows forms event handlers to be named with a lower-case letter.</Description>
		</Rule>
		<Rule Name="OpeningCurlyBracketsMustNotBePrecededByBlankLine" CheckId="EX1509" DisabledByDefault="true">
			<Context>An opening curly bracket must not be preceded by a blank line.</Context>
			<Description>Validates that an opening curly bracket is not preceded by a blank line. Based on SA1509 behaviour, but allows using nested code blocks.</Description>
		</Rule>
		<Rule Name="ElementsMustBeDocumented" CheckId="EX1600" DisabledByDefault="true">
			<Context>The {0} must have a documentation header.</Context>
			<Description>Validates that an element contains a properly formatted documentation header. Based on SA1600 behaviour, but allows windows forms event handlers to be undocumented.</Description>
		</Rule>
		<Rule Name="ConstructorSummaryDocumentationMustBeginWithStandardText" CheckId="EX1642" DisabledByDefault="true">
			<Context>The documentation text within the constructor's summary tag should be "Initializes a new instance." or should begin with the text: "{0}".</Context>
			<Description>Verifies that a constructor's summary text begins with the appropriate wording. Based on SA1642 behaviour, but allows any constructor to have the following summary text: "Initializes a new instance.".</Description>
		</Rule>
		<Rule Name="DestructorSummaryDocumentationMustBeginWithStandardText" CheckId="EX1643" DisabledByDefault="true">
			<Context>The documentation text within the destructor's summary tag should be "Finalizes an instance." or should begin with the text: "{0}".</Context>
			<Description>Verifies that a destructor's summary text begins with the appropriate wording. Based on SA1643 behaviour, but allows any destructor to have the following summary text: "Finalizes an instance.".</Description>
		</Rule>
	</Rules>
</SourceAnalyzer>
